Charles M. Renaud records, 1897-1942 (bulk 1914-1922)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Charles M. Renaud records, 1897-1942 (bulk 1914-1922)
AZ 252
Renaud, Charles M.
Journals, customers' accounts, invoices, inventories, correspondence, and related business records of Renaud's mercantile operations. Some records relate to former owners and partners, Soto Brothers of Wilcox, Ariz., 1897. Includes account balances for Shannon Copper Co., Clifton, Ariz., 1906-1909.
4.5 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL:http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
Charles M. Renaud was the owner of mercantile stores in the mining towns of Pearce, Gleeson, and Courtland, Arizona.
Scope and Content Note
Journals, customers' accounts, invoices, inventories, correspondence, and related business records of Renaud's mercantile operations. Some records relate to former owners and partners, Soto Brothers of Wilcox, Ariz., 1897. Includes account balances for Shannon Copper Co., Clifton, Ariz., 1906-1909.
Access Terms
Soto Brothers and Company
Shannon Copper Company (Clifton, Ariz.)
Retail trade -- Arizona -- History -- Sources
Merchants -- Arizona -- History -- Sources
Pearce (Ariz.) -- History -- Sources
Journals
Accounts
Inventories
Container List
- Suspense Ledger. 1903-1914 (Box 1)
- Cash Book. December 17, 1917-December 12, 1918 (Box 1)
- Correspondence. 1907-1932 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Income tax returns. 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous bills. 1907-1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Shannon Copper Co., Clifton, Arizona: Miscellaneous papers. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Soto Bros. and Chattman: Bills. 1897 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous items. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Journals. 1917-1942 (Box 2)
  Includes journals from:
  March 1917-November 1917
  June 1922-January 1926 (bound with January-May 1942)
  January 1928-December 1928
  February 1930-September 1936
  March 1938-February 1940
  April 1940-October 1942
- Invoices. January 1928-June 1928 (Box 3)
- Invoices. July 1928-December 1928 (Box 4)
- Customers' accounts, A-M. (Box 5)
- Customers' Accounts, N-Z. (Box 6)
- Separate Ledger, A-Z. 1909-1922 (Box 7)
- Inventories. 1914-1922 (Volume 8)